Hi, in this lesson I will show you how to use inline shot, not only for auto-liter view
but also for integrated terminal.
With console inline shot, you can ask questions, get some suggestions, direct in the
code editor you place where you have the console, or you can also get help with some
shell commands within the integrated terminal.
In my chat I want you to state in the flow of your work without having to switch to
separate chat view.
It can be useful when you want to apply some changes or ask some questions about selected
parts of the code.
The first use case you can ask some questions, for example you can select a code, you can
pick command + key to see the inline shot, I will type them.
In the case I use right here, if you use window you can use control + key.
And for example, we selected part of code, we can change the mode, we have three modes,
edit selection, edit two file or quick questions, we also can send to the chat if we need
to work, get some more detailed answers, like we want to do some bigger edits, let's
choose mode quick questions and ask what this check does.
Let me see an answer, this check can choose both from and two currencies exist in the
rate object.
If not, if it's missing, we through enter also, okay it's clear, we can close it.
We can also ask how some matter, some hooks work, so you can use it, another use case we
can refactor some selected parts of the code, for example what you can do, like I want
to return the only convert to the mount right here, I select this part of the code, click
command + key, I use edit selection and return just a converted mount right here and you
see the change, so we can accept or reject it.
If you want to accept, there is a shortcut, command + y and command + enter rejected, you
can use it, okay, we can also select the whole method, for example ask to refactor it, but
I will use, I want to select the code, I will use the edit full file mode and you ask an
optimise, convert method, let's see what it will suggest, it's generating, it's syncing
how it can be optimised, okay what it does, edit some checks, I don't really want, I
ask it to optimise it, not to add some checks, let's say no, let's reject it and ask
to make the word method more short, result to many variables inside and now we see it much
shortened, just one line instead of I have lines, oh we can accept it, we can click accept
files, this is how to use edits across the full files, okay, now let's see how work
is terminal, you can click on terminal and you turn it out to open it, or you can also
use some shortcut shift + command + back tick and open it, and in terminal we can ask different
commands about, for example files or folders we have, for example how to use some commands
let's ask command key, we have a question mode and let's ask what files I have, as you
see it's just as the command how we can check it, just click enter to apply the command
and I see the list of the files we have in this folder, okay, for example it can be useful
if I want to use git to commit some commands, how I can make my first commit, you see it
suggests us to use git add dot, that all the files and then through the ampersand, apply
another command right here and commit the first message, so if you don't know git commands
you can also ask file cursor to help you with it, okay, also if you click command key right
here in the detail you can also choose the models, if you just disable auto mode, you can
choose one of the models, you can add more models, so if you want to use the specific
model to get an antlers on your prompts, when you can use an auto mode which burns quality
and speed and recommended for most tasks because it can save your tokens, your rate limits
when you work with it, okay, I hope it was useful for you and now you know more how to
ask some questions about specific services, selected parts of code or ask question in
terminal and see you in the next lesson.